Aki…
阿秋…
Don't die.
你别死喔
When I die…
当我死了…
I hope you can cry for me.
希望你能为我哭泣
Snake, swallow it.
蛇 整个吞了
Return.
回去
The Fiend ran away.
魔人逃之夭夭了
We just need Chainsaw's heart.
目标只有电锯的心脏
No need to go after her.
不必追上去
I'll cut him in half this time.
这次就把他劈成两半
Don't damage his heart.
小心别伤到心脏
I don't really get this.
虽然我搞不太懂状况
But I think it's safe to say you are bad guys.
但我至少猜得到你们是坏蛋
I just love bad guys.
我超爱坏蛋
Because nobody's gonna complain when I kill them.
因为杀掉了也不会被谁唠叨
I'll put you down again.
我要再把你碎尸万段一次
Die!
去死
This is Sawatari.
我是泽渡
We're fighting with Chainsaw
正在练马西大楼三楼与电锯交战
Bring backup.
快来支援
Take this!
看招
Ow!
好痛
Do we shoot, sir?
要开枪吗？
Aim for his arms or his heart.
瞄准手臂或心脏
Yeah?
该死
Bastards!
混账东西
That really hurts!
痛死我了
What?
怪了
When did I get cut?
我什么时候被砍伤的？
That hurts!
很痛耶
Hey! Bad guy!
那边的坏蛋
This guy is one of you, right?
这家伙是你们的同伴吧
What if he is?
是的话又如何？
If you move even one millimeter,
敢动一毫米试试看啊
his face is gonna turn into mincemeat.
看我直接把你同伴的脸剁成肉酱
You little piece of…
这个混蛋…
That's right.
很好
Just stay there.
乖乖坐在原地
He disappeared?
消失了？
I'll carry him.
把这家伙搬走吧
You go get the car.
快点把车子开过来
Hurry up.
动作快
Although Chainsaw's friends should all be shot dead by now…
虽然电锯的同伙应该都死于枪下了
Devil Hunters are only human.
恶魔猎人终究是人类
They can't win against guns.
势必赢不了枪
They have guns…
是枪…
We're almost at the station.
马上就会到站
Move to another carriage and blend in with the civilians.
我们去别的车厢 混进普通人里吧
KYOTO STATION
（京都站）
Ms. Tendo.
天童小姐
We got word that Special Divisions 1, 2, 3, and 4 were all ambushed in Tokyo.
听说在东京 特异一、二、三、四课皆遇袭了
No way.
不会吧…
Is Ms. Makima dead?
真纪真小姐死了吗？
So we waited here for nothing?
那我们不就白等了吗？
Kurose.
黑濑
Tendo.
天童
I came under gunfire on the bullet train.
我在新干线上遇到枪击事件
There are bodies that need to be cleaned up.
车上有尸体需要处理
The luncheon is canceled.
饭局先取消
There was gunfire in Tokyo too…
在东京也发生了枪击案…
Ms. Makima, that blood…
真纪真小姐 身上那些血是…
Were you shot?
哪里中枪了吗？
It's not mine.
这是溅上来的血
I wasn't shot.
我没有中枪
Seems like it's total chaos over there.
那边似乎一片兵荒马乱
We haven't got any specifics.
尚未收到确切情报
Checking the casualties right now.
目前正在确认受害状况
Excuse me…
请问…
Should we go to Tokyo to assist?
应该立即赶去东京支援吗？
We won't make it in time.
现在过去也来不及吧
Their target is probably Denji.
敌人的目标恐怕是淀治
We'll deal with it here.
就在这里设法应对吧
Kurose, request for 30 convicts serving life sentences or worse
黑濑 你去找法务省借30名 判无期徒刑以上的罪犯
Tendo.
天童
Rent out a nearby shrine at the highest altitude possible.
把这附近海拔最高的神社直接包下来
And…
还有…
get me some clean clothes.
帮我准备替换的衣物
Where are we going?
我们要去哪里？
God knows.
天晓得
Quiet!
那边的 安静
Ms. Makima.
真纪真小姐
They're almost there.
他们差不多快抵达了
Thank you, Tendo.
谢谢你 天童
I'll be there soon.
我马上过去
Hurry up!
快点
I won't be able to fight for a while.
我暂时没办法战斗了
Yeah.
嗯
He's heavy.
好重
Come help me!
快来帮忙
Alright.
好啦
Grab that side.
你抬那边
Where am I supposed to hold?
要抓哪里才好啦？
What the hell?
感觉怪怪的 怎么搞的？
Why are you freaking out?
你在那边慌张什么？
Grab it!
快抬
Something feels wrong!
感觉有哪里不对劲？
What do you mean--
是什么样的感觉…
Team E!
E组
Have Team C reconfirm Makima's death!
叫C组重新确认真纪真死了没
This is Team E.
这边是E组
We've been unable to contact Team C for--
我一直联系不上C组…
That woman…
那个女人…
Why do we need blindfolds too?
为什么连我们都要蒙住双眼？
Ms. Makima reports directly to the Chief Cabinet Secretary.
真纪真小姐是内阁官房首长 的直属恶魔猎人
Ordinary Devil Hunters are not authorized to know
不容基层恶魔猎人知道 她与什么恶魔签订了契约
Repeat after me… Shuzou Mishima.
跟着我念…三岛修造
Shuzou Mishima.
三岛修造
Put him in the van!
快把电锯搬过来
Y-Yes!
好
In the van, now!
快搬到车上
Mishima!
三岛
Say, Takashi Inoue.
跟着我念 井上隆
Takashi Inoue.
井上隆
No!
不要
Somebody help me!
谁来救救我？
It stopped.
停下来了
You can remove those now.
可以拿掉了
I've finished what I can do from here.
我在这里能做的事都做完了
I'm returning to Tokyo.
我要回东京了
This ridiculous power… It's probably Makima.
看这个荒唐的能力 八成是真纪真
Let's escape while we still can.
趁还安全的时候快逃
Damn it!
该死
Isn't she dead?
不是已经杀掉她了吗？
You two…
你们两个…
are the shooters, right?
就是枪击犯吧？
Snake. Tail.
蛇
What is she, a monkey?
她是猴子吗？
Damn it!
可恶
Die inside the van!
要死就上车再死
Sorry about trying to kill you last time.
对不起 我上次还想杀了你
Why am I still saying that?
我怎么在为那件事道歉？
What am I doing?
什么跟什么？
No. I got too high…
不行 我不小心太兴奋了
He protected me…
为了保护我…
It… It's my fault…
我…是我害的…
For me, he…
就为了我…
I can't take it anymore…
我不行了…
This job is driving me crazy…
开始做这份工作后我就变得怪怪的…
When I see Ms. Himeno, I'll tell her I'm quitting…
一见到姬野前辈 就跟她提离职吧…
Madoka, glad to see you're alive.
圆 你还活着 真是太好了
How many in the Special Division survived?
特异课有多少人活下来？
Special Divisions 1, 2, 3, and 4 all came under gunfire.
特异一、二、三、四课
Almost all the humans died.
除了非人类之外 几乎死光了
A shooting specifically targeting the Special Division…
只针对特异课展开枪杀行动
The Gun Devil is very likely involved.
十之八九与枪之恶魔有关
I have an order from the superiors.
收到上级的命令
Due to the shortage of personnel,
由于人员不足
all four Special Divisions will merge into one.
特异一、二、三课将与四课合并
Tokyo Special Division 4
公安对魔特异四课
will be under your command from now on.
今后交给真纪真小姐坐镇指挥
Also, this is for you.
另外还有这个
What is it?
这是什么？
My resignation.
我的辞呈
You're quitting?
你不做了吗？
It's getting sinister in the Special Division.
特异课的火药味越来越浓厚
It's either quit or die.
那就只能辞职或等着殉职
I see.
这样啊
I have one last question for you.
最后请回答我一个问题
I can't discuss Public Safety's internal affairs with civilians.
公安内部机密不能透露给普通市民
Thank you for your service, Madoka.
圆 一直以来谢谢你
I'll pass this on.
我会帮你转交的
Well…
对了…
Ms. Makima.
真纪真小姐
It's not like we're joining your Special Division.
我们不会加入特异课喔
We're just here as advisors.
我们只是过来指导的
We'll be on our way back to Kyoto in one week.
一星期后马上就回京都
That's a shame.
真可惜
There are so many great restaurants in Tokyo.
东京有不少好吃的餐厅呢